reversenum.com 2012-04-01

# ReverseNum Privacy Policy

We want you to understand how we collect, use and safeguard information which you provide to us so that you can make an informed decision about using this web site.

Information Collected and How it is Used 

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: Web site use information collected automatically on an aggregate basis as you browse our Web site, and personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis.

Information Collected and Stored Automatically 

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the Web site, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

  * The Internet domain (for example, "xyzcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "myschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our Web site;
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
  * The date and time you access our site;
  * The pages you visit;
  * and If you linked to the ReverseNum Web site from another Web site, the address of that Web site.

We use this information to help us make our site more useful to members and other visitors - to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits. IP addresses are not linked to identifiable information.

If You Send Us Personal Information 

If you choose to provide us with personal information -- by sending an e-mail, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through our Web site -- we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. We do not share the information you give us with any entity, public or private, unless required by law. We do not create individual profiles with the information you provide. We do not collect information for marketing and do not sell any information provided by users through this Web site to third parties.

If you choose to buy a tracer report, your personal information will be used solely to for that purpose. Credit card information is handled through a third-party and not stored on our servers.

The use of, and access to your personal information is limited to those individuals who need to know that information to provide services or support to you. We strive to maintain only that degree of personal information necessary to provide you with the service and convenience that you expect from us.

Personal Information and Choice 

You may choose whether to provide personal information online. 

"Personal information" is information about a natural person that identifies a specific individual. Personal information includes such things as an individual's name, address, and phone number. A domain name or Internet protocol address is not considered personal information.

We collect no personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us by sending us e-mail, participating in a survey or completing an online form. You may choose not to contact us by e-mail, participate in a survey, or provide any personal information using an online form. Your choice not to participate in these activities will not impair your ability to browse this Web site and read or download any information posted on the site.

Email Warning 

Email is not a secure medium. Personal information sent via the Internet can be intercepted. You may, therefore, wish to reconsider the advisability of sending messages that contain highly sensitive, personal information to this Internet address.

ReverseNum does not voluntarily divulge personal information collected or information disclosed, however, you should be aware that we may be required to do so pursuant to State or Federal law.

If you believe that your personal information is being used for a purpose other than what was intended when submitted it, please contact the individual shown in the "Contact Information" section of this privacy policy.

Cookies 

Cookies are simple text files stored on your computer by Internet Web sites to help identify users and customize user experience. ReverseNum does not use cookies.

Security 

ReverseNum, as developer and manager of this Web site has taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of its data and prevent unauthorized access to information maintained. These measures are designed and intended to prevent corruption of data, block unknown or unauthorized access to our systems and information, and to provide reasonable protection of private and personal information in our possession. This Web site takes every precaution to protect users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and offline. When you are asked to enter personal information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with secure sockets layer encryption software. We also protect user information offline.

Disclaimer 

ReverseNum's Web site and materials may contain hypertext or links to other Internet computer sites which are not owned, operated, controlled or reviewed by ReverseNum. These links are provided solely as a courtesy and convenience to you, the visitor. When you link to one of these sites, you are no longer logged on to ReverseNum Web site and this privacy policy will not apply to the linked Web site, but rather you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

ReverseNum exercises no control over the organizations, views, accuracy, copyright or trademark compliance or the legality of the material contained on those servers and does not sponsor, endorse, or approve the information, content, products, materials, opinions or services contained on such external sites. The visitor proceeds to these external sites at their own risk. ReverseNum specifically disclaims any and all liability from damages which may result from the accessing of a third party site which is linked to ReverseNum Web site, or from reliance upon any such information.
